Guide to the Yale School of Music Grade Books
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale School of Music grade books
1906-1996
RU 562
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
4.5
The materials consist of grade books of professors from the Yale School of Music.
Yale School of Music
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 28-F (YRG 28-F), Student records of the Yale School of Music.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of grade books of professors from the Yale School of Music.
Grade books; Yale School of Music; Yale University -- Students
- Grade books, 1906-1961; Accession 1974-A-004
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2037
  - Grade Books
    - 1906/07-1917/18 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1917/18-1920-21 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1920/21-1922/23 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1923/24-1925/26 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1925/26-1927/28 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1927/28-1928/29 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1928/29-1929/30 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1930/31 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 1931/32-1932/33 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1932/33-1933/34 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 1933/34 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 1934/35-1935/36 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1935/36-1936/37 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 1936/37-1937/38 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 1937/38-1938/39 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 1938/39 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 1938/39 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - 1939/40 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - 1939/40-1940/41 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - 1940/41 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - 1940/41-1941/42 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 1941/42-1942/43 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - 1943/44-1945/46 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 1945/46-1946/47 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - 1946/47-1947/48 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - 1948/49-1950/51 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - 1950/51-1955/56 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - 1956/57-1960/61 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Student Record Cards, 1924-1945 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Class Records, 1952-1954 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Secondary voice grades, 1986-1996; Accession 2003-A-007
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2072
  - SPRING -1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - FALL -1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - SPRING -1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - FALL -1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - SPRING -1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - FALL -1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - SPRING -1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - FALL -1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - SPRING - 1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - FALL -1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - SPRING -1993 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - FALL -1993 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - SPRING -1994 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - FALL -1994 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - SPRING -1995 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - FALL -1995 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - SPRING - 1996 (Box 2, Folder 17)